1st-art-gallery.com 2018-10-02

# Privacy Policy | 1st Art Gallery

Your privacy and security are important to us.

#### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

We only gather information that visitors to 1st-art-gallery.com are willing to give. Some of it is required to fulfill orders (like names, shipping addresses, and phone numbers) or to maintain accounts (such as customer accounts and affiliate accounts) and we ask for some information so that we can provide better service (contact information like email addresses and phone numbers, for example). We don't store sensitive information like credit card data.

#### Sharing Information with Third Parties

We do not share our customers’ personal information with anyone. Period.

#### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us or :

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct the data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you (if you'd like your information deleted, send us an email request).
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data (By the contact us).

#### Non-Identifying Information

We collect all kinds of statistics about visits to our site, where the visitors came from, what they did and viewed during their visit, what kinds of computers and browsers they use, and where they went when they left. However, we do not (and cannot) collect any personally identifying information (names, email addresses and such) this way.

#### Privacy

1st-Art-Gallery maintains a strict privacy protocol for all customer information. Occasionally, we email our customers to let them know about new products, services, offers, promotions, and anything else we think might be of interest (unless you don’t want us to, in which case just let us know and we won’t). We keep all the email we receive and send so that we can find all the information we need about particular order histories. We send email to customers only if it concerns a specific order or question, or if the customer has opted to receive promotional emails.

#### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever you submit sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. We don't store any sensitive information.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
